https://www.polargear.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
By using our website you agree to our
cookie policy.
X
Name
Email
Menu
ShopBottlesAquarius waterGym bottlesPersonalised bottlesFood to goCool BagsFood BoxesIce PacksKidsPink, blue & unicornsToy StoryLOL SurpriseDisney PrincessMarvelDisney FrozenSpiritBBC Go JettersDespicable Me FluffyStar WarsFootballMinionsPolar Gear KidsPeppa PigHot DrinksBabyBecome a stockistBottlesFood to goKidsPersonalise
Account
Delivery free or £3.95*
Free for orders over £20*
BPA free
Safety for all the family
Go reusable
Save waste each day
Range of designs
For all the family
Privacy Policy
DNC UK Ltd Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. This policy covers what data we collect and how we use your information.
Key points from our policy:
• Use of your data: We are likely to use your information to fulfil your orders, monitor activity on our website and to provide you with marketing emails (if you opt in to agree to emails).
• Marketing: If you allow, we’ll send you news and offers with marketing, such as marketing emails. You are able to stop us sending you marketing information at any time by unsubscribing through newsletter footers or emailing us at gdpr@dnc-uk.com
Privacy statement objective
Under the EU regulation for General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), DNC is committed to protecting and securing your personal information. This privacy policy details how we collect and use personal information in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This statement does not form part of any contract to provide services. We may update this statement at any time. It is important that you inform us of any changes to your personal information which we hold so that the information which we hold is accurate and current. Please do not use the DNC website, purchase any products over the telephone with our customer services team, or enter our competitions or promotions unless you agree with this policy. We may amend this policy at any time and update this page for you to review when you wish.
Who we are
DNC UK Ltd is a company registered in England, our company number is 3707210, registered as: DNC UK Limited, The Old School, Princes Road, Weybridge, KT13 9BN. We have a data privacy manager to oversee compliance with this privacy policy. If you have any questions about this privacy notice or how we handle your personal information, please contact our privacy manager at gdpr@dnc-uk.com.
Information we collect
When you register with us or place orders we collect information from you, some of which is mandatory to deliver orders, some of which is voluntary. This can include name, email address, company addresses, payment details, your website addresses, your competition entries, and requests via our website. We collect information from use of the website with cookies; read more here. We do not keep a record of credit/debit card details. We will never ask you to supply credit card details via email or text message.
How we use your information
We collect information in order to process your order, manage your account and (if you agree) to send marketing emails with offers and product news. Marketing emails are not mandatory for use of our website and, if you prefer, you are able to unsubscribe from receiving these emails at any time via links at the bottom of every email newsletter. When needed, a contact name, address and contact information may be shared with couriers for delivering your order. We will not sell your information to third parties, or share it for marketing purposes without asking for your permission.
Viewing your information and requesting changes:
You have a right to view, edit or remove your information. You may unsubscribe from emails in newsletter footers, or email us at any time about your information on gdpr@dnc-uk.com.
Updates to our privacy policy: we keep our policy up to date on this page. Last update: September 2019.
Other links: Terms of use for using this website
Please note our privacy policy applies to this website only. If you visit another website, you should review their policy.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Sign up
Don't show anymore
